

Jozef Bachorik

Kukučínova 233/3, Bytča 01401, Slovak Republic • +421948918183 • jozefbachorik@gmail.com

Date of birth: 29. 8. 1994

Front-end engineer with 9 years of experience in building web applications. My current focus is the modern JavaScript stack - React 18, Next.js 14, and TypeScript - including server-side rendering (SSR/ISR) and deployments on Vercel. I am seeking remote/hybrid/fulltime B2B/freelance engagements with teams across the EU or US.

WORK EXPERIENCE

External supplier - frontend, Webmax s.r.o. - Žilina, Slovak Republic

September 2019 - Currently

Implementation of graphic design on the page, template creation, or backend when editing or creating components

External supplier - frontend, Poski.com s.r.o - Ostrava, Czech Republic

March 2018 - May 2019 implementation of graphic design on the site, production and modification of templates

EDUCATION

Faculty management science and informatics, University of Žilina

informatic

September 2013 - May 2016, Žilina, Slovak Republic

Bytča Gymnasium

General focus

September 2004 - May 2013, Bytča, Slovak Republic Eight-year study

SKILLS

HTML 5 - Expert

CSS - Expert

JavaScript - Advanced

TypeScript - Advanced

jQuery - Expert

Next JS - Advanced

ReactJS - Advanced

GIT - Advanced

PHP - Skillful

WordPress - Advanced

SilverStripe CMS - Expert

LANGUAGES

English - Upper intermediate (B2)

German - Elementary (A2)

Additional information

Next references:

personal creation:

- -bmwelding.sk
- -jozefbachorik.sk

Work for Identiq frontend(creation of elements and templates based on GN):

- -https://www.vahostav-sk.sk/
- -https://www.mamud.sk/
- -https://www.viveus.sk/
- -https://roderik.sk/
- -https://www.animavets.sk/